academicinfo.net 2005-03-08

# Academic Info: Privacy Statement

[](http://click.linksynergy.com/fs-bin/click?id=XthyH3U2rHQ&offerid=47491.10000024&type=4&subid=0) Home | Search | Index | [ Contact](mailto:madin@academicinfo.net) | Test Prep | Degree Programs | Student Center | Study Break | [ Bookstore](http://www.academicinfo.biz/) | Advertise

## Academic Info  
Privacy Statement 

Academic Info respects the privacy of all visitors to our educational directory. We do not lend, sell, or otherwise provide to a third party any personal information obtained from viewers of our site, including but not limited to, names, email or IP addresses, or demographic information of any kind. 

Academic Info does not collect personal information on our respected visitors. We do obtain anonymous statistical information but this information is not shared in any way.  To sign up for our monthly announcement list does require providing us with a valid email address but we do not sell, rent, or otherwise provide to a third party any email addresses collected. We do not use the email address collected for any purpose other than send out the viewer requested monthly email What's New announcement list.

Huge Savings on Scholarly and General Books at our [Bookstore](http://www.academicinfo.biz/). 

Home | Search | Index | [ Contact](mailto:madin@academicinfo.net) | Test Prep | Degree Programs | Student Center | Study Break | [ Bookstore](http://www.academicinfo.biz/) | Advertise

Last modified **October 2004**  
The Privacy Statement added April 2000.Copyright © 1998-2004 Academic Info.  All rights reserved.

  URL:  http://www.academicinfo.net/privacy.html
